export const CardData = [
  { front: "front: question here 1", back: "back: answer here 1", difficulty: "easy", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 2", back: "back: answer here 2", difficulty: "medium", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 3", back: "back: answer here 3", difficulty: "hard", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 4", back: "back: answer here 4", difficulty: "easy", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 5", back: "back: answer here 5", difficulty: "medium", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 6", back: "back: answer here 6", difficulty: "hard", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 7", back: "back: answer here 7", difficulty: "easy", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 8", back: "back: answer here 8", difficulty: "medium", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 9", back: "back: answer here 9", difficulty: "hard", image: "placeholder"},
  { front: "front: question here 10", back: "back: answer here 10", difficulty: "easy", image: "placeholder"},

]
// export default CardData